<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- array main category (0=info , 1=hotel, 2=food , bar=3, events=4 , places=5) -->
    <string-array name="categories">
        <item>Info</item>
        <item>Hotels</item>
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Bar</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Places</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- array info =>  info_desc = desc | info_desc_1 = itemName | info_web_1 = web -->
    <string-array name="info_desc">
        <item>As the centre of European culture and institutions, Brussels has much more to offer than most people imagine. Apart from its famous chocolates and beers.</item>
        <item>Brussels airport is fairy close to the city center. The distance is 12 kilometres (7 miles) and the fastest travelling time is an 18 minute drive.</item>
        <item>If you’re spending some time in Belgium, whether in the Brussels-Capital Region or in outlying cities, you can find accommodations to fit your needs, taste and budget.</item>
        <item>Tourist bus is a comfortable way of sightseeing without getting tired from managing the whole tour.</item>
        <item>For travelers who prefer to see the sights rather than bury their nose in a travel guide. there are guided sightseeing and topic tours available all over Brussels.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="info_desc_1">
        <item>Belgium\\'s fascinating capital, and the administrative capital of the EU, Brussels is historic yet hip, bureaucratic yet bizarre, self confident yet unshowy, and multicultural to its roots. All this plays out in a cityscape that swings from majestic to quirky to rundown and back again. Organic art nouveau facades face off against 1960s concrete developments, and regal 19th-century mansions contrast with the brutal glass of the EU’\s Gotham City. This whole maelstrom swirls out from Brussels’\ medieval core, where the Grand Place is surely one of the world’\s most beautiful squares.</item>
        <item>However, since Brussels is a busy European city, you really should have a time reserve and make proper travel research beforehand.There is a train going from Brussels Zaventem Airport to Brussels Central Station every 10 minutes between 5am and midnight, 7 days a week. The ride takes 18 minutes and costs €12,70. However you will need to deal with public transport from the central station to your hotel. If you think you will not like that after a flight then consider the taxi option below.</item>
        <item>You can find a bed in a Brussels hostel for around €17 - €25 per night. There are hostels located 15 minutes walk from the main square, but many are further away. Therefore make sure to look at the map too. Hostel atmosphere is quite friendly and it is a very good place to meet fellow travellers. Many people who travel on their own like to sit in the common room during the evening and chat. Or even plan their sightseeing together.</item>
        <item>It costs €32 for 48 hours and covers most Brussels attractions. Many people choose to do the whole circle around city first. To look around, listen to audioguide (in most world languages) and after that hop off to see the attractions.The Brussels hop-on hop-off bus goes around the city and stops at famous attractions. You can get off-board, check out the attraction and continue the route by getting on another bus whenever you feel like it.</item>
        <item>Most of them have multi-lingual guides available who speak English, French, German, Dutch, Russian and Arabic. Private tours for only your friends or relatives are also available.Brussels beer tasting tour. Within an atmosphere of authentic out-of-sight Brussels taverns, you will taste beers and pair them with foods. A 4 hour tour of beer and food guided by a beer expert with 20 years of experience.Brussels chocolate tour. By the end of this tour you will understand how to choose quality chocolate and why Belgium is so famous for it. And as you are walking between chocolate shops, sightseeing and monument history commentary will brighten your way. There is also a short chocolate workshop at the end of the tour.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="info_web_1">
        <item>https://goo.gl/qWxDLT</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/vkmfUf</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/qZZUsU</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/yty9yQ</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/rFsDF7</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- arrays  (number) = category array)-->
    <array name="cat_title_name">
        <item>@array/title_name_1</item>
        <item>@array/title_name_2</item>
        <item>@array/title_name_3</item>
        <item>@array/title_name_4</item>
        <item>@array/title_name_5</item>
    </array>
    <array name="cat_item_name">
        <item>@array/item_name_1</item>
        <item>@array/item_name_2</item>
        <item>@array/item_name_3</item>
        <item>@array/item_name_4</item>
        <item>@array/item_name_5</item>
    </array>
    <array name="cat_address">
        <item>@array/address_1</item>
        <item>@array/address_2</item>
        <item>@array/address_3</item>
        <item>@array/address_4</item>
        <item>@array/address_5</item>
    </array>
    <array name="cat_tel">
        <item>@array/tel_1</item>
        <item>@array/tel_2</item>
        <item>@array/tel_3</item>
        <item>@array/tel_4</item>
        <item>@array/tel_5</item>
    </array>
    <array name="cat_web">
        <item>@array/web_1</item>
        <item>@array/web_2</item>
        <item>@array/web_3</item>
        <item>@array/web_4</item>
        <item>@array/web_5</item>
    </array>
    <array name="cat_desc">
        <item>@array/desc_1</item>
        <item>@array/desc_2</item>
        <item>@array/desc_3</item>
        <item>@array/desc_4</item>
        <item>@array/desc_5</item>
    </array>
    
    <!-- array cat1 => hotel =>  title_name_1 = titleName | address_1 = address | tel_1 = tel | web_1 = web | desc_1 = desc | item_name_1 = itemName -->
    <string-array name="title_name_1">
        <item>Hotel Made In Louise</item>
        <item>Hotel des Galeries</item>
        <item>9 Hotel Sablon</item>
        <item>Hotel Saint-Géry </item>
        <item>Hotel The Neufchatel</item>
        <item>Hotel Le Dixseptième</item>
        <item>Hotel Welcome</item>
        <item>Hotel Esperance</item>
        <item>Vintage Hotel Brussels</item>
        <item>hotel Odette en Ville</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="address_1">
        <item>Rue Veydt 40 \n1050 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue des Bouchers 38 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>rue de la Paille 2 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Place Saint-Géry 29 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue de Neufchatel 34 \n1060 Brussels</item>
        <item>rue de la Madeleine 25 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Quai au Bois à Brûler 23 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue du Finistère 1 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue Dejoncker 45 \nBrussels</item>
        <item>Rue de Chatelain 25 \n1050 BRUSSELS</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tel_1">
        <item>003225374033</item>
        <item>003222137470</item>
        <item>003228800701</item>
        <item>003222040620</item>
        <item>003225373725</item>
        <item>003225171717</item>
        <item>003222199546</item>
        <item>003222191028</item>
        <item>003225582600</item>
        <item>003226402626</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="web_1">
        <item>https://www.madeinlouise.com</item>
        <item>http://hoteldesgaleries.be</item>
        <item>https://www.9-hotel-sablon-brussels.be</item>
        <item>http://www.hotelstgery.com/</item>
        <item>http://www.hotelneufchatel.be/</item>
        <item>http://www.ledixseptieme.be/</item>
        <item>http://www.hotelwelcome.com</item>
        <item>http://www.hotel-esperance.be</item>
        <item>http://vintage-hotel.brussels-hotels.net</item>
        <item>http://www.odetteenville.be</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_1">
        <item>Hotel Made in Louise is a three-star hotel located just 300 meters from Avenue Louise in Brussels. From the Louise metro station, you can easily travel through the beautiful city of Brussels. The European Parliament is only a 15-minute walk from the hotel. The 39 modern rooms at the Hotel Made in Louise have a bathroom with a rain shower and free toiletries. Some rooms have bathtubs and other rooms have lovely views of the courtyard. Enjoy the freshly prepared breakfast buffet. There are good restaurants near the hotel.</item>
        <item>Hotel des Galeries is located in the historical heart of Brussels. The hotel is less than a two-minute walk from the Grand Place and Manneken Pis and five minutes from Brussels Central Station. Hotel des Galeries offers 23 modern and soundproofed rooms. The rooms have wooden floors and a dressing room. An iPod dock and a Nespresso coffee machine are available. Each room has a private bathroom with a bath, shower, toiletries and bathrobes. Let yourself be tempted by the à la carte restaurant, 1 Michelin star, it serves only homemade Belgian dishes.</item>
        <item>The 9 Hotel Sablon is not a hotel, it\'s a marvel in the heart of Brussels. It is in the artistic district of Sablon in Brussels that our new boutique hotel, 9 Hotel Sablon, has been nestled. Faithful to a contemporary and timeless design, this trendy hotel is located in the heart of Brussels, and shakes up all the codes of the traditional hotel industry. Indeed, with artistic inspiration it is like the apartment of an art collector. This boutique hotel in Brussels is a work of the studio Castel Veciana Arquitectura, where from the facade a mark of elegance and simplicity emanates from this place.</item>
        <item>Hôtel Saint-Gery is a boutique hotel set in a classic mansion in Brussels city center. I is located next to the lively Antoine Dansaert street and 350 meters from the Grand Place. Hôtel Saint-Gery has 24 modern rooms with modern interiors and original wooden floors. All rooms have a private bathroom with free toiletries. On the ground floor of the hotel you will find the jazz bar De Belmonte. Here you can enjoy music and delicious tapas. You can have breakfast there every morning.</item>
        <item>Hotel The Neufchatel is a boutique hotel that has been decorated by interior designer Manuel Vraux S. Laranjeiro. The hotel is just a five-minute walk from Avenue Louise. By tram, you can easily reach the Grand Place, the Manneken Pis, the Atomium and the BruExpo exhibition grounds. The Neufchatel Hotel is an excellent choice if you like shopping, museums and fine dining. The stylish 20 rooms at The Neufchatel Hotel are tastefully furnished and include a private bathroom with a rain shower. The Saint-Gilles district is the ideal place to visit Brussels and enjoy the many restaurants and cafes.</item>
        <item>Hotel Le Dixseventh is located in the heart of Brussels, just 240 meters from the UNESCO World Heritage Grand Place. The Magritte Museum is just 500 meters from the Hotel Le Dixseventh. The hotel combines historic details with luxurious decor and modern amenities. The 24 elegant rooms of the Hotel Le Dixseptième are fully equipped and some rooms are located in the modern wing of the hotel. Hotel Le Dixseventh has a large public area with a bar (very comfortable chairs) and a fireplace. There is also an intimate garden courtyard.</item>
        <item>Welcome Hotel is located in the city center of Brussels on Place Sainte-Catherine, known for its many cafes, bars and restaurants. The hotel is just ten minutes walk from the Grand Place. You can travel easily to Brussels from Sainte-Catherine metro station, located near the hotel. The Welcome Hotel offers 16 unique rooms decorated with works of art, it\'s unique, you\'ll see! The colorful rooms all include luxurious bathrooms. Start the day with fresh bread and croissants in the Parisian-style café-bar.</item>
        <item>Hôtel Espérance in Brussels is a small hotel with 13 rooms. This small Art Deco hotel is quietly located in the heart of Brussels, just off Rue Neuve. Each of its design rooms has a unique style and décor. The bathrooms are luxuriously decorated and feature either a spacious shower or a spa bath. A buffet breakfast is served daily at Esperance Tavern, which features stained glass windows and Art Deco decorations. The staff of the Hotel Esperance is at your disposal and will do everything in its power to make your romantic weekend in Brussels a success.</item>
        <item>Vintage Hotel Brussels is decorated in the style of the 70s. The Vintage also includes an elegant wine bar with character and a spacious terrace in the courtyard, so you do not necessarily need to leave the hotel. On a sunny afternoon, you can enjoy a drink on the terrace for a wonderful time. The 29 rooms of the Vintage Hotel are fully equipped so that even in your living room you will have a good time. Vintage Hotel is just 50 meters from the trendy shopping district of Avenue Louise.</item>
        <item>Boutique-Hotel located in the heart of the Châtelain district in a beautiful 1920\'s mansion. The place has kept the intimate and exclusive atmosphere of traditional hotels and the quality of the service. The elegant rooms are decorated with fine materials and Italian marble. Each has extra large beds. Odette en Ville has a library and a collection of DVDs and offers daily newspapers. The Hotel Odette en Ville has only eight rooms but all very intimate.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="item_name_1">
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- array cat2 => food =>  title_name_2 = titleName | address_2 = address | tel_2 = tel | web_2 = web | desc_2 = desc | item_name_2 = itemName -->
    <string-array name="title_name_2">
        <item>La Trinacria</item>
        <item>Le Toukoul</item>
        <item>La Quincaillerie</item>
        <item>Fin de Siècle</item>
        <item>Belga Queen</item>
        <item>Le Cercle Des Voyageurs</item>
        <item>La Truffe Noire</item>
        <item>Mer du Nord</item>
        <item>L’Idiot du Village</item>
        <item>Au Vieux Bruxelles</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="address_2">
        <item>Tomberg 257 \n1200 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue de Laeken 34 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue du Page 45 \n1050 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue des Chartreux 9 \n1000 Brussel</item>
        <item>Rue fossé aux loups 32 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue des Grands Carmes 18 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Boulevard de la Cambre 12 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue Ste Catherine 45 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue Notre Seigneur 19 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>rue Sainte-Boniface 35 \n1050 Brussels</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tel_2">
        <item>003222656276</item>
        <item>003222237377</item>
        <item>00325339833</item>
        <item>003225129049</item>
        <item>003225129049</item>
        <item>0032475347411</item>
        <item>003225143949</item>
        <item>003225131192</item>
        <item>003225025582</item>
        <item>00322503311</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="web_2">
        <item>http://www.latrinacria.be</item>
        <item>https://www.toukoul.be</item>
        <item>https://www.quincaillerie.be/</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/4eUiQM</item>
        <item>http://www.belgaqueen.be</item>
        <item>https://www.lecercledesvoyageurs.com/</item>
        <item>http://www.truffenoire.com</item>
        <item>http://vishandelnoordzee.be</item>
        <item>http://www.lidiotduvillage.be</item>
        <item>http://www.auvieuxbruxelles.com</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_2">
        <item>The restaurant "La Trinacria" is located in Tomberg. And welcomes you in its Italian setting, to taste its typical Italian dishes. All our dishes are also takeaway, which is why we give the possibility to the customers to order their dishes by telephone and internet. And so come pick them up once ready. We also work with billing (only for companies) do not hesitate to contact us for more information. A business lunch and suggestions will be offered every week with dishes totally different from our menu to satisfy all our customers.</item>
        <item>Ethiopian restaurant and cultural house Toukoul is as beautiful as it is exotic, its fabulous interior designed by Belgian photographer Serge Anton, with sculptures and unique pieces brought straight from Ethiopia. One of the best things about Toukoul is its program of weekend concerts, with jazz, blues and lounge performed by talented local artists. Feast on the best injera (a sourdough pancake) in town, topped with the delectable wot and spicy key wot sauces, or the succulent tibs – fried meats smothered in aromatic spices – while you listen to the soft sounds coming from Toukoul’s intimate stage. Don’t leave without trying the intense Addis Flower cocktail, and make sure you book a table a few days in advance – this is one of the most popular venues in Brussels.</item>
        <item>Named after its location in a historic ironmonger’s shop, La Quincaillerie is a striking example of Art Deco architecture, where elements of brass are coupled with heavy, wooden accents to create an ambiance of times gone by. The cuisine is similar in its approach, combining tradition with contemporary elegance. Start your meal at the exposed oyster bar, and go on to taste carefully prepared French-inspired classics, with ingredients sourced directly from local producers and the restaurant’s own farm in Bresse. Unsurprisingly, La Quincaillerie is a favorite fixture in the elegant Châtelain neighborhood, and a great place to dine after an afternoon spent at the Victor Horta Museum nearby.</item>
        <item>Universally acclaimed as one of the best spots for authentic fare in the capital, Fin de Siècle is all about the heavy, hearty flavors of Belgian cuisine – get ready to taste the classic sausage and stoemp (mashed potatoes) smothered in a thick sauce, the ever-local carbonnade – Belgium’s answer to the Hungarian goulash, and numerous other delicacies best washed down with a glass of beer. The setting is basic and convivial, but Fin de Siècle has the kind of charm that makes it an instant favorite with guests, who always come back for more. Make sure you get there early; the restaurant doesn’t accept bookings and there’s always a queue thanks to its popularity and location right by Saint-Géry.</item>
        <item>Stained glass ceilings, contemporary sculpture, marble columns – Belga Queen is a stunning example of 19th century Bruxellois architecture, nestled in a former bank and revamped with the modern taste in mind. Designed by Antoine Pinto of Pinto &amp; Co fame, it breathes sophistication both in its unique decor and on the menu, which presents an eclectic mix of beloved classic and seasonal specials. Alternatively, the oysters and seafood platter are always good choices here – go for the Malines cockerel on a bed of gingerbread, sprinkled with peach syrup, or one of the luscious lobsters. Belga Queen is a fabulous spot for those seeking a taste of opulence with a touch of haute culture, right in the heart of the city.</item>
        <item>A peaceful oasis in the heart of central Brussels, just a stone’s throw from the infamous Manneken Pis, Le Cercle des Voyageurs welcomes travelers with a cozy atmosphere, soft music, travel books scattered around the room and rotating exhibitions of photography and paintings; no wonder the venue describes itself as an ‘art and travel café’. The menu is equally diverse, with delicious specials inspired by world cuisines. Go for the moqueca, a Brazilian fish stew, the North African méchoui or the Malines chicken with chicory and stoemp – straight from the Brabant province. However, Le Cercle des Voyageurs is perhaps best known for its live music nights and busy schedule of cultural events, so stay on after dinner and get a taste of local creativity.</item>
        <item>La Truffe Noire is more than a restaurant – it is a culinary institution dedicated to serving some of the most refined flavors in Brussels. The restaurant’s Michelin Star guarantees high quality, and its focus on creating culinary masterpieces with black and white truffles speaks for itself. Fans of this delicacy are in for a treat with superb dishes such as the luxurious whole-cooked Périgord truffle on toast and truffle butter, or the more conventional truffle-filled ravioli. La Truffe Noire sits at the edge of the beautiful and often overlooked Jardins de l’Abbaye de la Cambre, the perfect spot for a leisurely post-dinner stroll. For a slightly more central location on Avenue Louise, visit the sister restaurant Atelier de la Truffe Noire, which has more of a bistro vibe to it</item>
        <item>More of a fish bar than restaurant, Mer du Nord (or Noordzee in Flemish) is one of those places you could only find in Brussels. Don’t expect to be seated; this is a standing affair, with high tables set around a large, semi-circular bar, outside at the picturesque Place Sainte-Catherine. Make your order at the bar (there is a whiteboard that lists the catch of the day), choose a table, wait for the server to call out your name and pick up your plate, laid with some of the freshest fish and seafood in the city and sprinkled with Mer du Nord’s house tartare sauce. The best strategy here is to order several smaller plates and share them around – the prawns are to die for, while the kibbeling – deep-fried slices of Atlantic cod – is a signature delicacy you shouldn’t miss out on.</item>
        <item>Perched on a narrow street on the way from the Eglise Notre-Dame de la Chapelle to the flea market at Jeu de Balle, L’Idiot du Village looks like one of the many antique shops that surround it. Colorful, quirky and irresistibly charming, with pieces of vintage furniture and accessories strewn around the room as if on an erratic whim, L’Idiot offers a truly unique dining experience in the heart of the Marolles. The food is less unorthodox than the decor, but by no means boring; the primarily French menu changes every season. Some of the most exciting delicacies in the past have included the roast pigeon served with artichoke risotto, or the foie gras terrine with a beet and cuberdon jelly.</item>
        <item>Au Vieux Bruxelles has been standing in the heart of St. Boniface since 1882, and can easily claim the title of the most Bruxellois restaurant in the area. Its charm is due to its simplicity, where wood-paneled walls, chequered table covers and countless memorabilia scattered around the room transport diners to another era. Expect to see the best of traditional Brussels fare on the menu, from the Gueuze beer carbonnade with chips to the waterzooi chicken stew and some of the best moules frites (mussels with chips) in town. However, be careful not to miss Au Vieux Bruxelles while walking by – the tumbledown exterior and plastic chairs set on the street outside do a great job at camouflaging this hidden gem of a restaurant</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="item_name_2">
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- array cat3 => Bar =>  title_name_3 = titleName | address_3 = address | tel_3 = tel | web_3 = web | desc_3 = desc | item_name_3 = itemName -->
    <string-array name="title_name_3">
        <item>Goupil Le Fol</item>
        <item>Le Cercueil</item>
        <item>KAFKA</item>
        <item>Ultime Atome</item>
        <item>Café Belga</item>
        <item>The Music Village</item>
        <item>La Porte Noir</item>
        <item>Etiquette</item>
        <item>La Pharmacie Anglaise</item>
        <item>Monk Bar</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="address_3">
        <item>rue de la violette 22 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue des Harengs 10 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue des Poissonniers 21 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue Saint-Boniface 14 \n1050 Brussels</item>
        <item>Place Eugène Flagey 18 \n1050 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue des Pierres 50 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>rue des alexiens 64 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Avenue Émile de Mot 19 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Coudenberg 66 \n1000 Brussels</item>
        <item>Rue Sainte Catherine 42 \n1000 Brussels</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tel_3">
        <item>003225111396</item>
        <item>0032497124565</item>
        <item>003225136631</item>
        <item>003225134884</item>
        <item>00326403508</item>
        <item>003225131345</item>
        <item>00322511783</item>
        <item>003226446411</item>
        <item>0032489560736</item>
        <item>003225117511</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="web_3">
        <item>https://www.facebook.com/Goupil.Le.Fol</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/A1Nr7B</item>
        <item>https://www.facebook.com/cafekafkabrussels/</item>
        <item>https://www.ultimeatome.be/</item>
        <item>https://www.facebook.com/cafebelgabrussels/</item>
        <item>https://www.themusicvillage.com/</item>
        <item>https://www.laportenoire.be/</item>
        <item>http://www.etiquette-wines.com</item>
        <item>https://www.facebook.com/lapharmacieanglaise/</item>
        <item>http://www.monk.be/</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_3">
        <item>With an intimist, mysterious and romantic atmosphere, this place is the closest venue you could compare to the state of mind of "Amélie Poulain". You feel like you\'re at home, sitting on couches even more comfortable than yours. What might be different is the occasional bicycle that is hanging from the ceiling or the family portraits that overlap each other on the walls. The Goupil le Fol is like a bar within a house; or a house within a bar? Weird, but well done.</item>
        <item>For more than 35 years, this is the most unusual meeting place around Grand Pace. A mortuary chamber, all dressed in black, as it should be, with real coffins serving as tables. This bar, far from being morbid, was at first frequented by the Brussels youth, then by the tourists who made this very special place one of their favorite landmarks.</item>
        <item>Kafka is just perfect for starting - or indeed finishing - the night off on a gentle note, despite stocking enough varieties of vodka and national beer to sink a fleet of battle ships.The decor is traditional. Oaken tables, oaken bar, old piano in the corner, panelled booths, a spiral staircase- it is all a welcome corrective to the tired formulae of the modernist.</item>
        <item>Smack bang in the middle of the lively cluster of bars and restaurants on Rue St-Boniface, this brasserie has rapidly become a firm favourite among locals, Serving a large array of excellent artisanal beers, a wine list that\'s particularly strong on French reds and a solid menu of Belgian classics, it attracts a young, if rather eclectic crowd, and has a welcoming, appealing atmosphere; it\'s a place you\'ll want to return to again and again.</item>
        <item>Café Belga is housed in the former offices of the national radio and television office. This place is like an institution for some people in Brussels who frequent Place Flagey on a daily basis. This is probably the most frequent bar in Place Flagey. It does not matter that this silk morning, noon or evening, you will find your happiness. Between breakfast, Sunday morning brunch, or after-work drink, Belga will delight you.</item>
        <item>Enjoying a 17th century location at the very heart of Brussels, only a few metres away from the legendary Grand’Place, the Music Village has opened its doors on the 1st of September 2000. With acoustics, sound system, lighting, stage, warm welcome, comfort, and food &amp; drink that live up to the most prestigious clubs of New-York and London, the Music Village offers all music fans, listeners and musicians alike, a return to the Golden Age of international jazz clubs.</item>
        <item>In the sixteenth century, the vaulted space currently occupied by the Black Gate, constituted the kitchens of the convent of the Alexians. We can still see a well and a cooler that served the sisters to cook and keep food. The Black Gate is now a place where, in the atmosphere, the products sold and the spirit of the bartenders, we find a Celtic and medieval side that suits so well to its vaults.</item>
        <item>Located in the district of La Cambre, Etiquette is a bar wine not quite like the others: here is self-service! Thanks to a prepaid magnetic card, one chooses his wine and the desired quantity (3, 6 or 12 cl). More than 50 bottles are waiting for us wisely behind a window, kept at a good temperature and kept with nitrogen. The opportunity to test many different wines without (too much) ruin.</item>
        <item>Notice to fans of surreal atmosphere and retro decor, you will be served. Immersed in another century, flasks and jars of formalin are inspected with a cocktail of Hendrick\'s gin. Here, beverages are real elixirs that you enjoy with your eyes closed. A barred universe, a real cabinet of curiosities to discover at least once, change of scenery guaranteed.</item>
        <item>On the border with the artsy Sainte-Catherine area, Monk Bar is the place to go if you’re looking for a spacious yet intimate bar with some style. Be sure to keep up-to-date with its schedule of live music and football games shown here, when the bar buzzes with atmosphere.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="item_name_3">
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
        <item>price: from 30€</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- array cat4 => events =>  title_name_4 = titleName | address_4 = address | tel_4 = tel | web_4 = web | desc_4 = desc | item_name_4 = itemName -->
    <string-array name="title_name_4">
        <item>Brussels Jazz Weekend</item>
        <item>Music Festival</item>
        <item>Roller Bike Parade</item>
        <item>Brussels Les Bains</item>
        <item>Ommegang</item>
        <item>Midi Fair</item>
        <item>Brussels Summer Festival</item>
        <item>Midi Market</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="address_4">
        <item>May 25/26/27</item>
        <item>June 21/22/23/24/25</item>
        <item>From 3rd June to \n09th September</item>
        <item>From 06 June to \n12 August</item>
        <item>the first Thursday \nof July</item>
        <item>from 14 July to \n19 August</item>
        <item>From 14 to 18 August</item>
        <item>Every Sunday 6h to 13h30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tel_4">
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="web_4">
        <item>http://www.brusselsjazzweekend.be/</item>
        <item>http://www.fetedelamusique.be/</item>
        <item>http://belgiumrollers.com/</item>
        <item>http://www.bruxelleslesbains.be/</item>
        <item>https://www.brussels.be/ommegang</item>
        <item>https://www.brussels.be/midi-fair</item>
        <item>https://www.brussels.be/bsf</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/ak1Yd2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_4">
        <item>The Brussels Jazz Weekend is a free festival that will give numerous jazz fans from the Brussels region and from far beyond, the opportunity to explore the city with the intoxicating, festive and warm sounds of Belgian and international jazz. In open air and in many venues and bars, the public will be able to enjoy live music, jazz in all it\'s forms: from swing to bebop, blues, rock and world music, depending on the tastes and the inspiration of the musicians who will give the best of themselves in order to make this festival unforgettable.</item>
        <item>June 20, 21 and 22! Note these dates in your diaries because during these three days, a wind of musical madness will blow on the French Community Wallonia-Brussels. For the 19th time in a row, the Music Festival will resume its rights by investing squares, gardens and dead ends to offer you more than 500 free concerts throughout Wallonia and Brussels. Many surprises in perspective: rock, pop, classical, jazz, electronic music, song, … all the ingredients will be gathered to make this party the rendezvous where everyone will find a shoe to his feet: the big ones, like the little ones . Music lover or amateur dilettante</item>
        <item>Every Friday from June to September, at 19h, this expedition on wheels embarks on a journey through one or more Brussels municipalities. This is the occasion of a beautiful ride on rollerblades or by bike, or on any non-motorized rolling object, on lanes usually reserved for cars. What discover the tunnels of the city differently! The event is also available throughout the country.</item>
        <item>In Brussels les Bains, once the entrance is crossed, visitors are instantly on holiday, away from the noise of cars and the bustle of the city, in a relaxed and summer.Somnolate in a deckchair, practice dances and the most varied sports, sunbathing on the hot sand, enjoying an aperitif, playing with the children, strolling between the chalets, watching an outdoor movie on a giant screen … For five weeks, festive spirits from all over a lot of novelties proposed this year. The Brussels beach has been the meeting place for all cultures, colors and trends.</item>
        <item>In the Ommegang, the streets of Brussels are filled with a parade of people in medieval costumes representing the various groups of the population, dignitaries and guilds of the time. Every year (on the first Thursday of July and the preceding Tuesday), the Ommegang passes through the streets of Brussels to Grand-Place. The current version is a reconstruction of the arrival into Brussels of Charles V and his court in 1549. This grand spectacle features hundreds of extras in magnificent garb.</item>
        <item>Every day, from 14 July to 19 August 2018, along the Boulevard du Midi, between the Porte de Halle and the Porte d\'Anderlecht. The traditional and gigantic Midi Fair stands along the Boulevard du Midi every year. Hundreds of attractions are there for young and old, some traditional, others the most modern.</item>
        <item>The Brussels Summer Festival makes the inhabitants of Brussels dance during the month of August. A new scene (the "Magic Mirrors" scene is making a big comeback), an app, foodtrucks and, most importantly, an explosive programming: this year again, the BSF promises a wonderful moment of entertainment! 125,000 visitors. So, ready to dance? Here are the 5 unmissable events that will take place in the capital from August 6 to 15.</item>
        <item>Rich in products coming from the 4 corners of the globe, you will find especially African specialties, Mediterranean but also typical Belgian stands. Real place of excitement where the sales technique is to shout louder than its neighbor, do not venture there if the crowd and the noise bother you. This market also gives pride of place to plants: shrubs, potted plants, flowers, seeds … Here you will find something to reboost your home or give new life to your tired garden. We also advise you to take a tour through the Spanish specialty store which is at the beginning of the market.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="item_name_4">
        <item>free access</item>
        <item>free access</item>
        <item>free access</item>
        <item>Leisure</item>
        <item>Historical</item>
        <item>Leisure</item>
        <item>Music Festival</item>
        <item>shopping</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- array cat5 => places => title_name_5 = titleName | address_5 = address | tel_5 = tel | web_5 = web | desc_5 = desc | item_name_5 = itemName -->
    <string-array name="title_name_5">
        <item>Grand-Place</item>
        <item>The Atomium</item>
        <item>Cinquantenaire Park</item>
        <item>Cathedral St. Gudula</item>
        <item>Mannekepis</item>
        <item>Museums Of Fine Arts</item>
        <item>Sablon and Marolles</item>
        <item>Galeries Royales St-Hubert</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="address_5">
        <item>Grand Place is the central square of the City of Brussels</item>
        <item>Heysel park, located in the west of Brussels</item>
        <item>The Parc du Cinquantenaire or Jubelpark is not only a park</item>
        <item>Its history goes as back as the 9th or even the 8th century</item>
        <item>Manneken-Pis was at first a fountain that played an essential role</item>
        <item>Discover this essential cultural centre in the heart of Brussels.</item>
        <item>The Sablon and the Marolles appear to be two extremes</item>
        <item>Right next to the Grand-Place, the Galerie de la Reine is home to lots of luxury boutiques</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tel_5">
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>NA</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="web_5">
        <item>https://goo.gl/jpN53Z</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/QJ4ogP</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/rn36Hc</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/9b3SM7</item>
        <item>https://www.brussels.be/manneken-pis</item>
        <item>https://www.fine-arts-museum.be</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/mvXM7F</item>
        <item>http://www.grsh.be/</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_5">
        <item>Grand-Place, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, is the main tourist attraction of the City of Brussels but its beginnings were less than glamourous. The area was just a swampy sand-bank between two brooks, known as ‘broek sella’ which gave Brussels its name. The sand bank was reclaimed and turned into ‘Niedermerckt’ (lower market) and sold French and English textiles, French wines and German beer.
            In the Middle Ages wooden houses were built around the market and by the 14th century wealthy families took to building stone mansions which led to the market developing into the main commercial administrative centre. The town hall came in 1402 and by now it was also a political centre. This is where dukes, royalty and emperors were received but the square was also the site of executions.
            Today the Grand-Place is a beautiful, wide open cobbled medieval and is Brussels’ main market square. It is a great place to hang out and admire the elegant guildhouses which replaced all the wooden homes. Many have admired its beauty including Victor Hugo and Baudelaire who rhapsodised about its charm and appealing looks.
            There is a daily flower market between March and October and often accompanied with concerts and a light show in the evening.
            Every two years, during the third week of August (next one will take place 16-19 August 2018), Belgian begonia cultivators decorate the Grand-Place with a beautiful flower carpet using around 750,000 begonias. Visitors are greeted with 3,200 square feet of amazing plant tapestry depicting a theme.
            The square is where daily business is done and where a flurry of local bars and cafés are a superb example of top quality café culture.</item>
        <item>Heysel park, located in the west of Brussels, is dedicated to recreation and leisure.
            One of the highlights of the park is the Atomium.The Atomium is a monument in Brussels, Belgium, built on the occasion of the 1958 World Fair and representing the conventional mesh of iron crystal enlarged 165 billion times.
            The Atomium was designed by the engineer André Waterkeyn and erected by the architects André and Jean Polak for the 1958 World Fair in Brussels, Belgium.
            It is a building halfway between sculpture and architecture that rises to 102 m. Its structural steel weighs 2,400 tons. Like the Manneken Pis and the Grand Place, it has become a symbol of Belgium\'s capital.
            It consists of a steel frame with nine spheres interconnected and originally coated with aluminum. The spheres have a diameter of 18 meters and weigh approximately 250 tons each. Symbolically, the Atomium embodies the audacity of an era that wanted to confront the destiny of humanity with scientific discoveries.
            The construction of the Atomium was a technical feat. Of the nine spheres, six are open to the public, each with two main floors and a lower floor reserved for service. The central tube contains the fastest elevator of the time (5 m / s) installed by the Belgian branch of the Swiss firm Schlieren (later taken over by Schindler). It allows 22 people to reach the top in 23 seconds.
            The escalators installed in the oblique tubes are among the longest in Europe. The largest is 35 m long.</item>
        <item>The Parc du Cinquantenaire or Jubelpark is not only a park but a national landmark in Brussels. The name means \'Park of the fiftieth anniversary\' and it was built during the reign of Leopold II to commemorate fifty years of Belgian independence.
            Symbolically, the Cinquantenaire Park in Brussels is built in the shape of a pentagon, like the inner and outer rings of the city. Cinquantenaire sits just outside the inner circle, and is close to the European Quarter.
            At the south eastern point of the park is a giant arch with two arms extending out. It is quite a monumental entrance. The two arms of the arch are home to three museums: The Autoworld, an art museum and an army museum.
            Visitors can climb to the top of the arch for free from an entrance in the army museum to see a nice view of Brussels and European Quarter. On a clear day, you will be able to see far and wide.
            What locals know is that the entire area is populated with international people working among European institutions and large corporations, which have offices in Brussels.
            In order to keep everyone entertained throughout the year this Brussels park plays host to an endless number of events such as concerts, club nights, festivals, drive-through-cinemas, environmental days, aperitifs, and even the starting line to Brussels marathons.</item>
        <item>The Cathedral of St. Michael and St. Gudula or ‘Collegiale Sint-Michiels- en Sint-Goedele-co-kathedraal’ in Dutch was given cathedral status in 1962 and the patron saints Michael and Gudula are also the patrons of the city of Brussels, which is where the cathedral is located.
            Its history goes as back as the 9th or even the 8th century, when sources believe that a chapel was built to honour St. Michael on the Treurenberg Hill. However, two centuries later, Duke of Brabant, Lambert II had a Romanesque church built in its place. In 1047, the relics of the martyr St. Gudula were transported here from the Saint Gaugericus Church on Saint-Géry Island and thus the cathedral became of two patron saints: Michael and Gudula and so did the city of Brussels.
            In the beginning of the 13th century, Henry I, Duke of Brabant commissioned the restoration of the cathedral, adding two round towers to it. In 1226, his successor Henri II ordered the renovation of the church. The period coincided with the appearance of the Gothic style and so the Gothic collegiate church came to be almost 300 years later. The cathedral was completed right before the reign of the emperor Charles V in 1519.
            Saint Michael is the Guardian of the Catholic Church and, as mentioned earlier, also the patron saint of Brussels ever since the Middle Ages.
            In Catholic writings, Saint Michael the Archangel is the defender of the Church, fighting Satan and helping lost souls in their final hours.</item>
        <item>The earliest mention of the existence of Manneken Pis can be found in an administrative text, dating from 1451–1452, about the water lines supplying the fountains of Brussels. From the beginning, the fountain played an essential role in the distribution of drinking water. It stood on a column and poured water into a double rectangular basin of stone.
            The only representations of this first statue can be found, very schematically, in a painting by Denis Van Alsloot, representing the Brussels\' Ommegang of 1615 and in a preparatory drawing to this painting.
            Towards the end of the 17th century, the statue became more and more important in the city life. It was also a survivor of the bombardment of Brussels in 1695. Manneken-Pis became a precious good and enjoys a ceaselessly growing glory.
            During big events, we adorn him with luxurious clothes. We know that in the 18th century, Manneken-Pis was dressed at least 4 times a year.
            Since he lost his main function in the network of water conveyance of the City in the 19th century, Manneken-Pis gradually became an image and symbol of the Brussels folklore, the joy of the inhabitants and their capacity of self-mockery.</item>
        <item>The Royal Museums of Fine Arts of Belgium contain collections of around 20,000 paintings, sculptures and drawings, which are preserved and studied.
            The RMFAB is comprised of several entities: the Musée Old Masters Museum, the Musée Modern Museum, the Musée Wiertz Museum and the Musée Meunier Museum, the Musée Magritte Museum and the new Musée Fin-de-Siècle Museum.
            The Musée Old Masters Museum houses art works from the 15th to the 18th century.
            The Museum of Modern Art covers the art from the late 18th century to the present day, mostly Belgian and French painting of the 19th and 20th Centuries.
            The Musée Wiertz Museum, which has preserved its original atmosphere, is dedicated to painter, sculptor and writer Antoine Wiertz (1806-1865)
            The Musée Meunier Museum is located at Ixelles in the house-workshop de Constantin Meunier (1831-1905)
            The Musée Magritte Museum presents an outstanding collection of works by the Belgian Surrealist artist René Magritte.</item>
        <item>The Sablon and the Marolles appear to be two extremes: on the one hand a chic and affluent neighbourhood, and on the other a working class neighbourhood, authentic and a little rough around the edges. Yet both imperceptibly overlap and influence each other.
            Sablon/Zavel and Marolles/Marollen seem to be the polar opposite of each other: one an elegant and prestigious neighbourhood, the other more down-to-earth, authentic and somewhat down-at-heel.
            Even so, these neighbourhoods flow into each other unnoticed and influence each other.
            Sablon/Zavel is a place for antiques, while in Marolles/Marollen the same antiques are on offer at the daily flea market for a song.
            Sablon/Zavel was once the aristocratic district of Brussels, but the rue Haute/Hoogstraat, which runs directly through the Marolles/Marollen neighbourhood, still holds its own.
            It already had a certain status in the 16th century. Part of the Marolles/Marollen is still influenced by the Sablon/Zavel: buyers with lots of capital are acquiring empty buildings in rue Blaesstraat or rue Haute/Hoogstraat and turning them into antiques businesses.
            Parts of Marolles/ Marollen are starting to look more and more like the Sablon/Zavel.</item>
        <item>gallery of the king and princes
            Conceived in 1837 by Jean-Pierre Cluysenaar, the Royal Galleries Saint-Hubert are inaugurated ten years later by King Leopold I. This monumental passage brings together the Queen\'s Gallery, the King\'s Gallery and the Galerie des Princes.
            By designing for the first time in the world a passage to the dimensions of the street, Jean-Pierre Cluysenaar has created a place that has become a link between the various functions of the city: cultural spaces, habitats, shops, offices, restaurants and cafes have been around for more than 150 years.
            Even today, the Queen\'s, King\'s and Princes\' Galleries are animated by 6 million passers-by-year. The passage is at the same time a microcosm, a place of memory and creation, where past, present and future intertwine inextricably.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="item_name_5">
        <item>Leisure</item>
        <item>Leisure</item>
        <item>Leisure</item>
        <item>Culture</item>
        <item>Culture</item>
        <item>Culture</item>
        <item>shopping</item>
        <item>shopping</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>