<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="pager_name">Tour</string>
    <!-- string for tabs -->
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="bar">Bar</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="places">Places</string>
    <!-- string main activity -->
    <string name="header_text">Brussels City Tour</string>
    <string name="footer_header">Belgium</string>
    <!-- string fragment info -->
    <string name="brussels_desc">As the centre of European culture and institutions, Brussels has much more to offer than most people imagine. Apart from its famous chocolates and beers.</string>
    <string name="brussels_desc_1"> Belgium\'s fascinating capital, and the administrative capital of the EU, Brussels is historic yet hip, bureaucratic yet bizarre, self confident yet unshowy, and multicultural to its roots. All this plays out in a cityscape that swings from majestic to quirky to rundown and back again. Organic art nouveau facades face off against 1960s concrete developments, and regal 19th-century mansions contrast with the brutal glass of the EU’s Gotham City. This whole maelstrom swirls out from Brussels’ medieval core, where the Grand Place is surely one of the world’s most beautiful squares.</string>
    <string name="brussels_desc_web">https://goo.gl/qWxDLT</string>
    <string name="brussels_airport">Brussels airport is fairy close to the city center. The distance is 12 kilometres (7 miles) and the fastest travelling time is an 18 minute drive.</string>
    <string name="brussels_airport_1"> However, since Brussels is a busy European city, you really should have a time reserve and make proper travel research beforehand.There is a train going from Brussels Zaventem Airport to Brussels Central Station every 10 minutes between 5am and midnight, 7 days a week. The ride takes 18 minutes and costs €12,70. However you will need to deal with public transport from the central station to your hotel. If you think you will not like that after a flight then consider the taxi option below.</string>
    <string name="brussels_airport_web">https://goo.gl/vkmfUf</string>
    <string name="brussels_accommodation"></string>
    <string name="brussels_accommodation_1">You can find a bed in a Brussels hostel for around €17 - €25 per night. There are hostels located 15 minutes walk from the main square, but many are further away. Therefore make sure to look at the map too. Hostel atmosphere is quite friendly and it is a very good place to meet fellow travellers. Many people who travel on their own like to sit in the common room during the evening and chat. Or even plan their sightseeing together.</string>
    <string name="brussels_accommodation_web">https://goo.gl/qZZUsU</string>
    <string name="brussels_attraction">Tourist bus is a comfortable way of sightseeing without getting tired from managing the whole tour. It costs €32 for 48 hours and covers most Brussels attractions. Many people choose to do the whole circle around city first. To look around, listen to audioguide (in most world languages) and after that hop off to see the attractions.The Brussels hop-on hop-off bus goes around the city and stops at famous attractions. You can get off-board, check out the attraction and continue the route by getting on another bus whenever you feel like it.</string>
    <string name="brussels_attraction_web">https://goo.gl/yty9yQ</string>
    <string name="brussels_guide">For travelers who prefer to see the sights rather than bury their nose in a travel guide, there are guided sightseeing and topic tours available all over Brussels. Most of them have multi-lingual guides available who speak English, French, German, Dutch, Russian and Arabic. Private tours for only your friends or relatives are also available.Brussels beer tasting tour. Within an atmosphere of authentic out-of-sight Brussels taverns, you will taste beers and pair them with foods. A 4 hour tour of beer and food guided by a beer expert with 20 years of experience.Brussels chocolate tour. By the end of this tour you will understand how to choose quality chocolate and why Belgium is so famous for it. And as you are walking between chocolate shops, sightseeing and monument history commentary will brighten your way. There is also a short chocolate workshop at the end of the tour.</string>
    <string name="brussels_guide_web">https://visit.brussels/en/toursforgroups</string>
</resources>
